Talent is relative.
Flora and Son is a music, comedy, drama film directed by John Carney.
Single mom Flora is at a loss about what to do with
her rebellious teenage son, Max.
Her efforts to keep him out of trouble lead to a beat-up acoustic guitar, a
washed-up LA musician, and harmony for this frayed Dublin family.
Flora, played by Eve Hewson.
Max, played by Orén Kinlan.
Jeff, played by Joseph Gordon-Levitt.
Ian, played by Jack Reynor.
Kathy, played by Marcella Plunkett.
Kev, played by Paul Reid.
Flora and Son is a 2023 musical comedy drama film written and directed by
John Carney, featuring original songs by Carney and Gary Clark.
The film stars Eve Hewson, Jack Reynor, Orén Kinlan, and Joseph Gordon-Levitt.
Flora and Son had its world premiere at the Sundance Film Festival on January 22, 2023, and was given a limited theatrical
release in the United States on September 22, 2023, to be followed by a wide release in Ireland on February 23, 2024.
It also began streaming on Apple TV+ worldwide on September 29, 2023.
It received positive reviews from critics and was named one of the top 10
independent films of 2023 by the National Board of Review.
The film explores themes of musical, dublin, ireland,
romance, single mother, teenage boy.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.